Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1969-1993; Accession 1999-A-091
  - Gursey CSDC 162A (Box 19, Folder 931)
  - Garland CSDC 160A (Box 19, Folder 932)
  - Rai CSTD 157A (Box 19, Folder 933)
  - Schoolfield CSTD 156A (Box 19, Folder 934)
  - Hartlyn CSTD CSJE 162A (Box 19, Folder 935)
  - Olson CSTD 158A (Box 19, Folder 936)
  - Brieff CSJE 159A (Box 19, Folder 937)
  - Wofford CSJE 157A (Box 19, Folder 938)
  - Rodgers CSJE 161A (Box 19, Folder 939)
  - Committee on Teaching in Residential Colleges Minutes (Box 19, Folder 940)
  - New England Nuclear (brown folder) (Box 19, Folder 941)
  - Berkeley College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 19, Folder 942)
  - Elliot CSBK 167b/ CSTC 167b (Box 19, Folder 943)
  - Roberge/ Yardley CSBK 165b (Box 19, Folder 944)
  - Clowes CSBK 166b (Box 19, Folder 945)
  - Hewitt CSBK 168b (Box 19, Folder 946)
  - Koizim CSTC 163b (Box 19, Folder 947)
  - Bayne CSMC 140b (Box 19, Folder 948)
  - Hansen CSBR 165b (Box 19, Folder 949)
  - Millington CSBR 166b (Box 19, Folder 950)
  - Wagner CSBR 167b (Box 19, Folder 951)
  - Wagner CSES 140b (Box 19, Folder 952)
  - Smith CSBR 164b (Box 19, Folder 953)
  - Bartlett CSCC 171bSpring 1980 (Box 19, Folder 954)
  - Calhoun College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 19, Folder 955)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges 1979 (Box 19, Folder 956)
  - Marmor/ White/ Robertson CSCC 170b/ CSJE 170b (Box 19, Folder 957)
  - Boyce & Hartmann CSCC 165b/ CSSY 165b (Box 19, Folder 958)
  - Osterweiss CSCC 172b (Box 19, Folder 959)
  - Storrs/ Barone CSCC 173b/ CSPC 173b (Box 19, Folder 960)
  - Storrs/ Barone TC/CC 65A (Box 19, Folder 961)
  - Storrs/ Barone CSCC/ CSJE 115b (Box 19, Folder 962)
  - Davenport College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 19, Folder 963)
  - Gibson CSDC 164b/ CSTC 164b (Box 19, Folder 964)
  - Amert CSDC/ CSJE 167b (Box 20, Folder 965)
  - Klein CSDC 169b/ CSBR 169b (Box 20, Folder 966)
  - Cantelon CSDC 165b (Box 20, Folder 967)
  - Froula CSDC 166b (Box 20, Folder 968)
  - Timothy Dwight College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 969)
  - Huang CSTD 159 (Box 20, Folder 970)
  - Henry CSTD 164b (Box 20, Folder 971)
  - Jonathan Edwards Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 972)
  - Snook and McHenry CSJE 165b (Box 20, Folder 973)
  - Russell CSJE 169b (Box 20, Folder 974)
  - Canemaker CSJE 164b/ CSSY 164b (Box 20, Folder 975)
  - Russell CSJE 171b/ CSDC 171b (Box 20, Folder 976)
  - Russell CSSY/ CSES 102A (Box 20, Folder 977)
  - Russell CSSY/ CSPC 90b (Box 20, Folder 978)
  - Russell CSUC 118b (Box 20, Folder 979)
  - Lish CC82A (Box 20, Folder 980)
  - Lish CSES 5A (Box 20, Folder 981)
  - Lish CSJE 163b (Box 20, Folder 982)
  - Lish CSJE 118b (Box 20, Folder 983)
  - diCorcia CSPC 172b (Box 20, Folder 984)
  - del Valle CSPC 170b (Box 20, Folder 985)
  - Bell CSPC 174b (Box 20, Folder 986)
  - Morse College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 987)
  - Baer CSMC 169b (Box 20, Folder 988)
  - MacKinnon CSMC 168b (Box 20, Folder 989)
  - McKinnon DC72A (Box 20, Folder 990)
  - Catherine Mackinnon CC26b (Box 20, Folder 991)
  - Arthur CSMC 167b (Box 20, Folder 992)
  - Kisselgoff CSMC 164b (Box 20, Folder 993)
  - Pierson Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 994)
  - Korsyn CSPC 169b (Box 20, Folder 995)
  - Saybrook Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 996)
  - Wertheimer CSSY 163b (Box 20, Folder 997)
  - Clark CSSY 164b (Box 20, Folder 998)
  - Ornston CSSY 113b (Box 20, Folder 999)
  - Reich CSSM 167b (Box 20, Folder 1000)
  - Bloom/ Feshbach CSSM 164b (Box 20, Folder 1001)
  - Edelstein CSSM 163b (Box 20, Folder 1002)
  - Nelson CSSM 166b (Box 20, Folder 1003)
  - Nelson CSBR 141b (Box 20, Folder 1004)
  - Ezra Stiles Spring 1980: Costs (Box 20, Folder 1005)
  - Lamm CSES 168 b/ CSSY 168b (Box 20, Folder 1006)
  - Karlsen CSES 163b (Box 20, Folder 1007)
  - Lea CSES 169b (Box 20, Folder 1008)
  - Roskies CSES 167b (Box 20, Folder 1009)
  - Caserio CSES 165b (Box 20, Folder 1010)
  - Lamm CSES 133A (Box 20, Folder 1011)
  - Fersh TC 82A (Box 20, Folder 1012)
  - Logue CSTC 171b (Box 20, Folder 1013)
  - Horvitz CSDC 148b (Box 20, Folder 1014)
  - Chessman CSTC 165b (Box 20, Folder 1015)
  - Slate CSBR 133A (Box 20, Folder 1016)
  - Schindel CSSM/ CSTC 186A (Box 20, Folder 1017)
  - Silver CSSM 181A (Box 20, Folder 1018)
  - Hannan CSES 195b (Box 21, Folder 1019)
  - Ezra Stiles Spring 1981: Costs (Box 21, Folder 1020)
  - Cormack CSIC/ CSSY 180A (Box 21, Folder 1021)
  - Collier CSTC/ CSBK 182A (Box 21, Folder 1022)
  - Donovan CSTC 183A (Box 21, Folder 1023)
  - McPeck CSDC 180A (Box 21, Folder 1024)
  - Bradford CSDC/ CSCC/ 186A (Box 21, Folder 1025)
  - Bradford CSDC/ CSCC 163A (Box 21, Folder 1026)
  - Papke CSDC/ CSCC 187A (Box 21, Folder 1027)
  - Papke CSDC 156A (Box 21, Folder 1028)
  - Roland CSCC/ CSJE 185A (Box 21, Folder 1029)
  - Berger CSCC/ CSDC 181A (Box 21, Folder 1030)
  - Cavanagh CSCC/ CSTD 188A (Box 21, Folder 1031)
  - Harris CSBR 182A (Box 21, Folder 1033)
  - Miller CSBK 183A (Box 21, Folder 1034)
  - Janeway CSDC/ CSCC 184A (Box 21, Folder 1035)
  - Skolnick CSDC 182A (Box 21, Folder 1036)
  - Skolnick CSTC 73bworkshop (Box 21, Folder 1037)
  - Skolnick CSTC 77b (Box 21, Folder 1038)
  - Thompson CSTD 184A (Box 21, Folder 1039)
  - Moore CSTD/ CSCC 182A (Box 21, Folder 1040)
  - Sung CSTD/ CSBK 181A (Box 21, Folder 1041)
  - Kinney CSJE/ CSBK 180A (Box 21, Folder 1042)
  - Gordon CSJE 181A (Box 21, Folder 1043)
  - Witt CSJE 183A (Box 21, Folder 1044)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges 1980-=81 (Box 21, Folder 1045)
  - Ha=iri CSMC 184A (Box 21, Folder 1046)
  - Hendler CSMC/ CSBR 183A (Box 21, Folder 1047)
  - Patterson CSMC 180A (Box 21, Folder 1048)
  - Carlesimo CSMC 182A (Box 21, Folder 1049)
  - Rescorla CSMC/ CSES 181A (Box 21, Folder 1050)
  - Jette CSPC 180A (Box 21, Folder 1051)
  - Thomas CSPC 184A (Box 21, Folder 1052)
  - Price CSPC/ CSSM 182A (Box 21, Folder 1053)
  - Price CSPC 158A (Box 21, Folder 1054)
  - Burgess CSSM/ CSPC (Box 21, Folder 1055)
  - Burgess CSSM/ CSMC (Box 21, Folder 1056)
  - Burgess CSCC/ CSSM 102A (Box 21, Folder 1057)
  - Roth CSSY 182A (Box 21, Folder 1058)
  - Silliman Spring 1981: Costs (Box 21, Folder 1059)
  - Cheresh-Allen CSSY 181A (Box 21, Folder 1060)
  - Cheresh CSSY 159A (Box 21, Folder 1061)
  - Pillsbury CSSY/ CSSM 184A (Box 21, Folder 1062)
  - Joyce CSSY 196b (Box 21, Folder 1063)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges 1980: Course Listings (no manilla folder) (Box 22, Folder 1064)
  - Berkeley College Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1065)
  - Turnbull CSBK/ CSPC 198b (Box 22, Folder 1066)
  - Sammons CSBK/ CSSM 197b (Box 22, Folder 1067)
  - Grant CSBK 191b/ CSCC 191b (Box 22, Folder 1068)
  - Kendrick CSBK/ CSJE 184A (Box 22, Folder 1069)
  - Wheeler & Gouls CSBK/ CSCC 194b (Box 22, Folder 1070)
  - Clarke CSBK 199 (Box 22, Folder 1071)
  - Branford College Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1072)
  - Glaser & De Lorenzo CSBR/ CSSY 192b (Box 22, Folder 1073)
  - Smith CSBR/ CSBK 196b (Box 22, Folder 1074)
  - Smith CSJE/ CSPC 160A (Box 22, Folder 1075)
  - Mezan CSBR 190b (Box 22, Folder 1076)
  - Calhoun Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1077)
  - Milch CSCC 195b (Box 22, Folder 1078)
  - Milch CSCC/ CSDC 161A (Box 22, Folder 1079)
  - Milch CSC 143b (Box 22, Folder 1080)
  - Milch CSCC 10A (Box 22, Folder 1081)
  - Auerhahn CSCC 192b (Box 22, Folder 1082)
  - Davenport Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1083)
  - Glickman CSDC 194b (Box 22, Folder 1084)
  - Stein CSDC 131A (Box 22, Folder 1085)
  - Freedman CSDC/ CSTC 191b (Box 22, Folder 1086)
  - Skolnick TC77A (Box 22, Folder 1087)
  - Stein CSDC/ CSBK 192b (Box 22, Folder 1088)
  - Timothy Dwight Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1089)
  - Busia CSTD/ CSMC 201b (Box 22, Folder 1090)
  - Davie, Townsend, and Lesser CSTD 201b (Box 22, Folder 1091)
  - Stepto CSTD/ CSSM 200b (Box 22, Folder 1092)
  - De Mayo CSTD 198b (Box 22, Folder 1093)
  - Jonathan Edwards Spring 1981: Costs (Box 22, Folder 1094)
  - Gorlin CSJE/ CSBK 200b (Box 22, Folder 1095)
  - Gorlin CSDC 168b/ CSJE (Box 22, Folder 1096)
  - RE CSJE/ CSSM Spring 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1097)
  - Gill CSJE 197b/ CSUC (Box 22, Folder 1098)
  - Morse Spring 1981: Budgets & Costs (Box 22, Folder 1099)
  - Hondler CSTD 112b (Box 22, Folder 1100)
  - Zabludowski (Box 22, Folder 1101)
  - Robinson CSPC 192b (Box 22, Folder 1102)
  - Carlin CSMC 190b (Box 22, Folder 1103)
  - Pierson Spring 1981: Budgets and Costs (Box 22, Folder 1104)
  - Lengyel CSPC/ CSMC 195b (Box 22, Folder 1105)
  - Montgomery PC 52A (Box 22, Folder 1106)
  - Mendoza CSPC 197b (Box 22, Folder 1107)
  - Neill CSPC 193b (Box 22, Folder 1108)
  - Halberstadt (Box 22, Folder 1109)
  - Saybrook Spring 1981: Costs and Expenses (Box 22, Folder 1110)
  - Shulman CSSY/ CSTC 185A (Box 22, Folder 1111)
  - Rand CSSY 190b (Box 22, Folder 1112)
  - Attwood CSSM/ CSBK 201b (Box 22, Folder 1113)
  - Mattar CSSM/ CSMC 196b (Box 22, Folder 1114)
  - Izysorski CSSM/ CSTD 195b (Box 22, Folder 1115)
  - Schneider CSSM/ CSMC 192b (Box 22, Folder 1116)
  - Mordden CSSM/ CSJE 190b (Box 23, Folder 1117)
  - Dennerline CSSM/ CSCC 193b (Box 23, Folder 1118)
  - Rodriguez CSES 180A (Box 23, Folder 1119)
  - Trumbull College: Budgets and Costs (Box 23, Folder 1120)
  - Shaw CSTC 192b (Box 23, Folder 1121)
  - Shaw CSTC 131A (Box 23, Folder 1122)
  - Slate CSTC 193b (Box 23, Folder 1123)
  - Mckinney CSTC 195b (Box 23, Folder 1124)
  - Collier CSTD/ CSES 87b (Box 23, Folder 1125)
  - Koizim CSTC 190b (Box 23, Folder 1126)
  - Sinnot- Armstrong CSES 182A (Box 23, Folder 1127)
  - Paul CSES 197b (Box 23, Folder 1128)
  - Besse CSES 192b (Box 23, Folder 1129)
  - Stein CSBK/ CSDC 190b (Box 23, Folder 1130)
  - Johnson CSPC 196b (Box 23, Folder 1131)
  - Van Den Pol & Green CSJE 195b (Box 23, Folder 1132)
  - Van Den Pol CSSM/ CSBK 185A (Box 23, Folder 1133)
  - Del Guidice CSTC 194b (Box 23, Folder 1134)
  - CSBK CSPC 208A Winks (Box 23, Folder 1135)
  - Bennett CSBK/ CSBR 205A (Box 23, Folder 1136)
  - Scheifner CSBK 209A (Box 23, Folder 1137)
  - Schott CSBK/ CSBR 206A (Box 23, Folder 1138)
  - Jervis CSDC 205A (Box 23, Folder 1139)
  - Romano CSDC 208A (Box 23, Folder 1140)
  - Hyatt CSCC/ CSUC 206A (Box 23, Folder 1141)
  - MacMullen/ Meeks CSCC/ CSUC 208A (Box 23, Folder 1142)
  - Terry CSCC/ CSSY 214A (Box 23, Folder 1143)
  - Kimball CSBR 184A (Box 23, Folder 1144)
  - Reynolds CSBK/ CSSM 207A (Box 23, Folder 1145)
  - Kimball CSBR/ CSBK 214A (Box 23, Folder 1146)
  - Brown CSJE/ CSES 211A (Box 23, Folder 1147)
  - Brown CSSY 131A (Box 23, Folder 1148)
  - Brown TD 79A (Box 23, Folder 1149)
  - Brown TD 50A (Box 23, Folder 1150)
  - Brown CSSY 161A/ CSES (Box 23, Folder 1151)
  - Mahoney CSJE 182A (Box 23, Folder 1152)
  - Lieberman CSJE/ CSDC 210A (Box 23, Folder 1153)
  - Anderson CSTD/ CSCC 210A (Box 23, Folder 1154)
  - Anderson CSTD 155A (Box 23, Folder 1155)
  - CSTD/ CSTC 211A Beatty (Box 23, Folder 1156)
  - CSUC 209A Singerman (Box 23, Folder 1157)
  - Milofsky CSUC/ CSBR 211A (Box 23, Folder 1158)
  - Hentschel CSUC/ CSCC 207A (Box 23, Folder 1159)
  - Van Den Pol CSUC/ CSBR 212A (Box 23, Folder 1160)
  - Van Den Pol CSMC 117b (Box 23, Folder 1161)
  - Van Den Pol CSSM/ CSES 91b (Box 23, Folder 1162)
  - Van Den Pol CSSM/ CSES (Box 23, Folder 1163)
  - Large CSPC/ CSSY 206A (Box 23, Folder 1164)
  - McGerr CSPC 209A (Box 23, Folder 1165)
  - Reiger CSPC/ CSCC 211A (Box 23, Folder 1166)
  - Krupp CSPC/ CSDC 207A (Box 23, Folder 1167)
  - Pittman CSPC 210A (Box 23, Folder 1168)
  - Oristaglio CSSY/ CSCC 212A (Box 23, Folder 1169)
  - Conaghan CSSY 210A (Box 23, Folder 1170)
  - Stepto CSSY 209A (Box 23, Folder 1171)
  - Price CSSM 209A (Box 23, Folder 1172)
  - Bruce- Novoa CSSM/ CSUC 205A (Box 23, Folder 1173)
  - Erlich CSSM 209A (Box 23, Folder 1174)
  - Crowley CSSM/ CSBK (Box 23, Folder 1175)
  - Crowley CSSM/ CSTD 120b (Box 23, Folder 1176)
  - Meyer CSSM 105 (Box 23, Folder 1177)
  - T. Anderson CSTC/ CSJE 209A (Box 23, Folder 1178)
  - Saxon CSTC 207A (Box 23, Folder 1179)
  - Spacks CTSC/ CSTD 208A (Box 23, Folder 1180)
  - Del Guidice CSTC 205A (Box 23, Folder 1181)
  - Hansen CSES 206A (Box 23, Folder 1182)
  - Seeley CSES 205A (Box 23, Folder 1183)
  - Berkeley College: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1184)
  - Ferber CSBK 216b (Box 24, Folder 1185)
  - Herrmann CSBK 223b (Box 24, Folder 1186)
  - Fayen CSBK 221b (Box 24, Folder 1187)
  - Fayen CSBK 155A (Box 24, Folder 1188)
  - Robert Kimball MC 24b (Box 24, Folder 1189)
  - Branford College: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1190)
  - Heller CSBR 219b (Box 24, Folder 1191)
  - Alvarez CSBR 208A (Box 24, Folder 1192)
  - Calhoun College: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1193)
  - W. Terry TC 42b (Box 24, Folder 1194)
  - W. Terry BR 69A (Box 24, Folder 1195)
  - High CSCC 218b (Box 24, Folder 1196)
  - Davenport: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1197)
  - Cole CSDC 220b (Box 24, Folder 1198)
  - Stein CSDC 219b (Box 24, Folder 1199)
  - Timothy Dwight: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1200)
  - Johnson CSTD 220b (Box 24, Folder 1201)
  - Weinstein CSTD 223b (Box 24, Folder 1202)
  - Endicott CSTD 215b (Box 24, Folder 1203)
  - Bourassa CSTD 222b (Box 24, Folder 1204)
  - Jonathan Edwards: Budgets and Costs (Box 24, Folder 1205)
  - Mahoney CSJE/ CSCC 220b (Box 24, Folder 1207)
  - Skinner CSJE 224 (Box 24, Folder 1208)
  - Morse College: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1209)
  - Laderman CSMC/ CSBK 216b (Box 24, Folder 1210)
  - Singerman CSMC 165b (Box 24, Folder 1211)
  - Baumann CSMC 218b (Box 24, Folder 1212)
  - Pope CSMC 217b (Box 24, Folder 1213)
  - A. Davis CSMC/ CSSM 219b (Box 24, Folder 1214)
  - Pierson: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1215)
  - McGerr CSPC/ CSBR 215b (Box 24, Folder 1216)
  - Pittman CSPC/ CSBR 220b (Box 24, Folder 1217)
  - Shestack CSPC/ CSBR 217b (Box 24, Folder 1218)
  - Saybrook: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1220)
  - Gray CSSY/ CSCC 205A (Box 24, Folder 1221)
  - Robert CSSY/ CSBK 217b (Box 24, Folder 1222)
  - Gorden CSSY/ CSSM 221b (Box 24, Folder 1223)
  - Gouwens CSSY/ CSJE 215b (Box 24, Folder 1224)
  - Crockett CSSY/ CSTD 218b (Box 24, Folder 1225)
  - Silliman: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1226)
  - Hansen CSES 217b (Box 24, Folder 1227)
  - Holmes (Box 24, Folder 1228)
  - Ferlo CSES 215b (Box 24, Folder 1229)
  - Rapaczynski CSES/ CSSM 222b (Box 24, Folder 1230)
  - Ezra Stiles: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1231)
  - Brand CSTC/ CSSY 219b (Box 24, Folder 1232)
  - Trumbull: Budgets & Costs (Box 24, Folder 1233)
  - Fersch CSTC 216b (Box 25, Folder 1234)
  - Wilson 225A CSMC/ CSPC (Box 25, Folder 1235)
  - Adair CSMC/ CSCC 232A (Box 25, Folder 1236)
  - Duran CSMC/ CSTD 230A (Box 25, Folder 1237)
  - Rudich CSMC/ CSSM 229A (Box 25, Folder 1238)
  - Rudich CSUC/ CSSM 213A (Box 25, Folder 1239)
  - Radford CSMC 227A (Box 25, Folder 1240)
  - Green CSMC/ CSBK 233A (Box 25, Folder 1241)
  - Scott CSMC/ CSBK 242b (Box 25, Folder 1242)
  - Ostfeld CSMC/ CSBK 231A (Box 25, Folder 1243)
  - Oblensky CSPC 227A (Box 25, Folder 1244)
  - Saybrook: Budgets & Costs (Box 25, Folder 1245)
  - King CSSY/ CSTD 227A (Box 25, Folder 1246)
  - Landauer CSSY/ CSBK 226A (Box 25, Folder 1247)
  - Sammons CSSM/ CSTC (Box 25, Folder 1248)
  - Burland CSSM/ CSCC 228A (Box 25, Folder 1249)
  - Smietanka CSSM 225A (Box 25, Folder 1250)
  - Bernstein CSES 225A (Box 25, Folder 1251)
  - Staden CSES/ CSPC 229A (Box 25, Folder 1252)
  - Smulyan CSES/ CSCC 227A (Box 25, Folder 1253)
  - Rai CSTC 228A (Box 25, Folder 1254)
  - Rai CSJE 60A (Box 25, Folder 1255)
  - Kuipers CSTC/ CSBR 227A (Box 25, Folder 1256)
  - Ginzberg CSTC/ CSCC 229A (Box 25, Folder 1257)
  - Simckes CSTC/ CSMC 226A (Box 25, Folder 1258)
  - Whitaker CSTC/ CSBK 225A (Box 25, Folder 1259)
  - Greene CSTC/ CSSM 232A (Box 25, Folder 1260)
  - Pease CSBK/ CSSY 228A (Box 25, Folder 1261)
  - Currier CSBR 228A (Box 25, Folder 1262)
  - Chavez CSBR/ CSBK 232A (Box 25, Folder 1263)
  - Nunes CSBR/ CSSY 229A (Box 25, Folder 1264)
  - Cook CSBR/ CSES 230A (Box 25, Folder 1265)
  - Cook CSBR 163b (Box 25, Folder 1266)
  - Cook CSBR CSCC 213A (Box 25, Folder 1267)
  - Cook BR 51A (Box 25, Folder 1268)
  - Darst CSCC/ CSSY 231A (Box 25, Folder 1269)
  - Darst CSCC/ CSBR 209A (Box 25, Folder 1270)
  - Ferraro III CSCC 226A (Box 25, Folder 1271)
  - Janeway & Potts CSDC 228A (Box 25, Folder 1272)
  - Beretz CSDC/ CSJE 226A (Box 25, Folder 1273)
  - Stark CSDC 225A (Box 25, Folder 1274)
  - Misiunas CSDC 229A (Box 25, Folder 1275)
  - Spence CSTD 225A (Box 25, Folder 1276)
  - Morse: Budgets & Costs (Box 25, Folder 1277)
  - Fersch Defeis CSMC/ CSSM 237b (Box 25, Folder 1278)
  - Pierson: Budgets & Costs (Box 25, Folder 1279)
  - Sarkonar CSPC/ CSJE 237b (Box 25, Folder 1280)
  - Jonhston CSPC 235b (Box 25, Folder 1281)
  - Johnston CSPC 218b (Box 25, Folder 1282)
  - Muson CSPC 236b (Box 25, Folder 1283)
  - Rabin CSSY 237b (Box 25, Folder 1284)
  - Archibald CSSY/ CSTD 238b (Box 25, Folder 1285)
  - Silliman: Budgets & Costs (Box 25, Folder 1286)
  - Wallace CSSY/ CSCC 242b (Box 25, Folder 1287)
  - Bronfeld CSSM/ CSJE 235b (Box 25, Folder 1288)
  - Storrs CSSM/ CSJE 247b (Box 25, Folder 1289)
  - Storrs CSSM 215b (Box 25, Folder 1290)
  - Biser CSSM/ CSMC 241b (Box 25, Folder 1291)
  - Ezra Stiles: Budgets & Costs (Box 25, Folder 1292)
  - Jackson & Klimovatskaya 244bCSES/ CSBR (Box 25, Folder 1293)
  - Trumbull: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1294)
  - Freccero CSTC/ CSES 238b (Box 25, Folder 1295)
  - Colonna-D=istria CSTC/ CSSM 242b (Box 25, Folder 1296)
  - Cosell CSTC/ CSJE 244b (Box 26, Folder 1297)
  - Cosell CSSM 166b (Box 26, Folder 1298)
  - Cosell CSSM 67b (Box 26, Folder 1299)
  - Cosell CSSM 121b (Box 26, Folder 1300)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges: Minutes and Course Listings (no Manilla folder) (Box 26, Folder 1301)
  - Zirkle CSBK 236b (Box 26, Folder 1302)
  - Mulvey CSBK/ CSSY 239b (Box 26, Folder 1303)
  - Mulvey CSSY 191b (Box 26, Folder 1304)
  - Mulvey CSPC/ CSBK 138A (Box 26, Folder 1305)
  - Mulvey CSSY 87b (Box 26, Folder 1306)
  - Mulvey CSSY 3b& CSBK 3b (Box 26, Folder 1307)
  - Berkeley: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1308)
  - Branford: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1309)
  - Chapanda CSBR/ CSES 242b (Box 26, Folder 1310)
  - Katrak 240bCSBR/ CSCC (Box 26, Folder 1311)
  - Solnit & Evans CSBR 245b (Box 26, Folder 1312)
  - Stark CSBR/ CSSM 238b (Box 26, Folder 1313)
  - Molnar CSBR/ CSTC 241b (Box 26, Folder 1314)
  - Calhoun: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1315)
  - Scobey CSCC 238b (Box 26, Folder 1316)
  - Lorimer CSCC 239b (Box 26, Folder 1317)
  - Lorimer CSCC 166b/ CSJE 166b (Box 26, Folder 1318)
  - Davenport: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1319)
  - Newton CSDC/ CSTC 236b (Box 26, Folder 1320)
  - Elliot CSDC 240b (Box 26, Folder 1321)
  - Gay CSDC/ CSBK 237b (Box 26, Folder 1322)
  - Stark CSPC 235b (Box 26, Folder 1323)
  - Timothy Dwight: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1324)
  - Wiseman CSTD 242b (Box 26, Folder 1325)
  - Beacham CSTD/ CSSY 241b (Box 26, Folder 1326)
  - Kinsley CSTD/ CSJE 246b (Box 26, Folder 1327)
  - Jonathan Edwards: Budgets & Costs 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1328)
  - Horn CSJE 239b (Box 26, Folder 1329)
  - Niese CSJE/ CSDC 242b (Box 26, Folder 1330)
  - Niese CSTD/ CSSY 198b (Box 26, Folder 1331)
  - Niese CSBK 141b (Box 26, Folder 1332)
  - Lubin CSJE/ CSES 241b (Box 26, Folder 1333)
  - Lubin CSSM/ CSBR 218b, 210b (Box 26, Folder 1334)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges Course Listings for 1983 (no manilla folder) (Box 26, Folder 1335)
  - Frackleton CSPC 252A (Box 26, Folder 1336)
  - Brumbaugh CSSY 249A (Box 26, Folder 1337)
  - Brumbaugh CSSY/ CSJE 207A (Box 26, Folder 1338)
  - Brunbaugh SY 51A (Box 26, Folder 1339)
  - Strauch CSSY/ CSBR 254A (Box 26, Folder 1340)
  - McCoy CSSY/ CSTC 248A (Box 26, Folder 1341)
  - Brennan CSSM/ CSCC 253A Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1342)
  - Guida CSSM/ CSTD 251A Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1343)
  - Collins CSSM/ CSCC 254A Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1344)
  - Fichera CSES/ CSPC 250A Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1345)
  - Fichera SM 81A (Box 27, Folder 1346)
  - Fichera CSJE 132A (Box 27, Folder 1347)
  - Shaviro CSES 251A (Box 27, Folder 1348)
  - Sodomskaya CSES/ CSCC 255A Fall 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1349)
  - Astrachan CSES 254A (Box 27, Folder 1350)
  - Goebel CSBK/ CSSY 251A (Box 27, Folder 1351)
  - Johnston CSBK 250A (Box 27, Folder 1352)
  - Murola CSBK/ CSMC 255A (Box 27, Folder 1353)
  - Brandenberg CSBR 253A (Box 27, Folder 1354)
  - Hicks CSBR/ CSMC 249b (Box 27, Folder 1355)
  - Hicks CSBR/ CSJE 243b (Box 27, Folder 1356)
  - Zonderman CSBR/ CSSM 256A (Box 27, Folder 1357)
  - Lazarre CSBR/ CSSY 252A (Box 27, Folder 1358)
  - Lazarre CSBR 226A (Box 27, Folder 1359)
  - Winchell CSBR 255A (Box 27, Folder 1360)
  - Eaton CSCC 249A (Box 27, Folder 1361)
  - Eaton CSBR/ CSSY 197b (Box 27, Folder 1362)
  - Eaton CSBR 168b (Box 27, Folder 1363)
  - Yastremski CSCC/ CSTD 248A (Box 27, Folder 1364)
  - Mahan CSCC/ CSJE 250A (Box 27, Folder 1365)
  - Mangini- Gonzalez CSDC 252A (Box 27, Folder 1366)
  - Marks CSDC/ CSBK 248A (Box 27, Folder 1367)
  - Grudinski- Gross CSTD/ CSTC 249A (Box 27, Folder 1368)
  - Kahn CSTP/ CSSY 255A (Box 27, Folder 1369)
  - MacIntyre CSJE/ CSES 248A (Box 27, Folder 1370)
  - MacIntyre CSES 191b (Box 27, Folder 1371)
  - Hughes CSJE 251A (Box 27, Folder 1372)
  - Fahey CSMC 254A (Box 27, Folder 1373)
  - Rosen CSMC/ CSPC 251A (Box 27, Folder 1374)
  - Warren CSMC/ CSJE 252A (Box 27, Folder 1375)
  - Pierson: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1376)
  - Abdulaziz H. Fahad CSPC 256b (Box 27, Folder 1377)
  - S. Phelps Platt Jr. CSPC 255A (Box 27, Folder 1378)
  - Sidney b. Silverman CSPC 260b (Box 27, Folder 1379)
  - Saybrook: Budgets & Expenses 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1380)
  - Robert E. Handschumacher CSSY 259b (Box 27, Folder 1381)
  - Samuel W. MacDowell CSSY 258b (Box 27, Folder 1382)
  - Silliman: Budgets & Expenses 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1383)
  - Camille A. Paglia CSSM 261b (Box 27, Folder 1384)
  - Paglia CSES 193b (Box 27, Folder 1385)
  - Ezra Stiles: Budgets and Costs 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1386)
  - Debbie Ward CSES 258b (Box 27, Folder 1387)
  - Jill Robbins CSES 257b (Box 27, Folder 1388)
  - Trumbull: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1389)
  - Shelley Fisher Fishkin CSTC/ CSTD 257b (Box 27, Folder 1390)
  - Fishkin CSJE/ CSBK 229A (Box 27, Folder 1391)
  - Fishkin CSTD/ CSJE 206A (Box 27, Folder 1392)
  - Katherine G. Keenum CSTC/ CSSY 261b (Box 27, Folder 1393)
  - Barbara b. McCorkle CSTC/ CSSM 259b (Box 27, Folder 1394)
  - McCorkle CSJE/ CSTD 240b (Box 27, Folder 1395)
  - McCorkle CSSM/ CSSY 216b (Box 27, Folder 1396)
  - CTRC Meetings- minutes 1983- 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1397)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Notes 1984- 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1398)
  - Berkeley: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1399)
  - Angela R. Holder CSBK 26b (Box 28, Folder 1400)
  - Stephen R. Clingman CSBK/ CSSY 260b (Box 28, Folder 1401)
  - Elliot LeibCSBK/ CSTD 259b (Box 28, Folder 1402)
  - Victoria Wyatt CSBK/ CSJE 257b (Box 28, Folder 1403)
  - Holder CSBK 218b (Box 28, Folder 1404)
  - Branford: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1405)
  - Olga Peters Hasty CSBR/ CSMC 258b (Box 28, Folder 1406)
  - Rodney J. McElroy CSBR/ CSCC 260b (Box 28, Folder 1407)
  - Bruce R. Sharpe CSBR/ CSES 259b (Box 28, Folder 1408)
  - Rena Grant CSBR/ CSSM 257b (Box 28, Folder 1409)
  - Amy Dru Stanley CSBR/ CSTD 264b (Box 28, Folder 1410)
  - Calhoun: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1411)
  - Elizabeth Mahan CSCC/ CSBK 263b (Box 28, Folder 1412)
  - Davenport: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1413)
  - Irena Grudzinska Gross CSDC/ CSCC 257b (Box 28, Folder 1414)
  - Donald Billingsley CSDC 263b (Box 28, Folder 1415)